Good morning, Flabébé!
Madatsubomi,
good morning to you too!
Woo! Poppo!
G’morn!
Huh?
What’s... that? A Pokémon?
Awesome!
It’s a huge balloon!
Navi, I’ve got an errand for you!
Okay!
We, the Rising Voltteccers,
have touched down in Miare City!
This place’s my hometown, after all!
And so, lemme give ya
the Miare City tour!
Lucario! Loudbone!
Doesn’t this take you back?
Wow! What a lovely city!
Whoa, and it’s full of Pokémon!
Hey, you dopes...
Listen to me, will ya?!
Ready, set, and... GO! READY! GO!
We’re in top-notch mode
You’re not alone, you know?
Put our palms together, raise them high, and let our lights unite
pOCket Monsters
Wonder Voyage
In rain, gales, or even blizzards
We can laugh together as friends
All of the gaps in the Index
let’s fill them in bit by bit
If you’re trying to be someone else
Don’t think like that
You’re fine just as you are
Don’t lose yourself
Recollect on what’s in your pocket
This is what makes us strong
A heartfelt bond that will never fade
Ready, set, and...
GO! READY! GO!
We’re in top-notch mode
You’re not alone, you know?
Let’s fly, higher and higher!
It’s fine to make mistakes
just rest your wings
When you’ve caught your breath
you can fly off once more!
Come along with us, oh-oh
Voltteccers
Pass the endlessly turning seasons,
and venture into brand-new skies
Miare City! A New Encounter
Hey!
I’ve been waiting for you two!
Huh? Ms. Matière?
What’s up with that getup?!
Yeah, it’s got detective vibes.
Right, Cap?
Doesn’t it just? Thank you!
Still, you sure have grown, Roy!
Oh! And you evolved into Loudbone!
That’s amazing!
And Ult... Welcome back.
Yeah... I’m back.
Yamirami looks well, too!
And!
Whoa! Ult, does that mean...?
It came outta the Dark Ball for me!
Right, Kairyu?
I see... So you’ve grown too, Ult...
That makes me so happy.
You fuss too much.
It ain’t no big deal!
Ms. Matière, these two are
from the Rising Voltteccers...
I’m Liko.
This is Masquernya.
I’m Dot.
And this’s Wanival.
I’ve been hoping to meet you.
I’m Matière.
This is Fluff.
Now, everybody!
C’mon in and chill!
Yeah!
I’ll put on some coffee.
Oh, that’s right!
I just ran out of beans,
so I sent my assistant out on an errand.
Errand? Assistant?
Matière! I got ‘em for ya!
Whoa!
So many Pokémon
I’ve never seen before!
Awesome!
Whoa-ho!
And there’s a Kairyu!
I’ve never seen one before! So cute!
Navi.
Oh, yeah.
Uhh... Are they guests?
Yeah. I told you, didn’t I?
These are Ult, Roy,
and the Rising Voltteccers.
Ahh!
Honest Roy and Shy Ult!
Huh?! What’s that about?
Oh, she’s...
I’m Navi!
Matière’s assistant.
Welcome to the Handsome House!
Nice to meet you!
So you like Pokémon.
Yeah! Navi loves Pokémon!
That smells great...
Navi wants some, too...
Remember what I said.
You aren’t old enough, Navi.
Awww!
Here! Have some special coffee milk!
Yay!
What’s with that?
It’s basically all milk.
Perfect for a little kid.
Nyah-nyah!
Treat someone like a kid,
and that makes you the kid.
Wha... didja say?!
Li’l kid!
Some famous Miare Galettes!
Yay! Navi loves these!
Huh? A group of adventurers? You guys?
Yeah, adventuring’s our job.
Even if you’re a li’l kid?
Huh?!
We go traveling around the world
with Pokémon and our friends.
With Pokémon?! Amazing!
Does that mean
you’ve seen all sortsa Pokémon?
Obviously! Anywhere we wanna go
is one quick hop away on the Brave Asagi!
“Brave”?
That’s our airship.
Ahh! Navi saw it in the morning!
This huge balloon, like bam!
And the ship’s captain is Cap.
Huh?! Mr. Captain?!
Navi wants to go for a ride!
Coming!
Did you need something?
Excuse me...
I have a request for a detective.
Here you go.
Thank you, miss.
I’m Navi, the detective’s assistant.
So, what was your request?
I’d like you to look for
this little one!
It’s a Melecie!
Yes, yes.
It’s such a shy, lonely sort,
and it’s never run off anywhere
all by itself before...
That is concerning.
How might I identify this Melecie?
This pendant...
My husband gave it to me,
and this shape...
Dear Melecie has
just the same shape on its chest.
I see... They do look alike.
Please, do whatever you can!
Right! I’m the detective entrusted with
keeping the peace in Miare, after all!
After all!
I had some detective work come in.
A search for a Pokémon, right?
That’s right. I’ll pop back in this evening,
so if you could look after Navi until...
Um!
Please let us help out, too!
If it’s no trouble, we’d like to
help find the old lady’s Melecie.
It’d let us see a detective’s work
firsthand, too!
Yeah! The more the merrier
when you’re lookin’ for Pokémon, after all.
That’s true...
Then how about I take you up on your kind offer?
Thank you very much!
Leave it to me!
Miare’s my home turf!
Then, you can be
the assistant’s assistant.
Lotta attitude comin’ from a little kid!
Nyah-nyah!
The old lady’s house is here.
If we go around
the Rose District, then...
This’s Navi’s helping!
All done!
Here.
Your helpings.
Thank you.
It smells great!
You gotta have coffee for
walking around Miare, after all.
Thank you.
And these’re the Pokémon’s helpings!
Got my detective set all ready too!
That’s a Dream Ball, isn’t it?
That’s right! Isn’t it cute?
Matière gave it me!
So? What Pokémon ya got?
Not telling!
Hmph! As if I wanted to know!
The two of you that haven’t been
to Miare before, come with me.
Right, thank you.
I’ll go check the plazas with Ult.
Yeah, leave ‘em to us!
And Navi!
We’ll go and question people.
Keep in contact
during the search, okay?
Right.
Then let’s get investigating!
Yeah!
Let’s start with the closest plaza.
This place’s huge, after all.
Hey!
Wouldn’t you be able to see everywhere
if you looked from the sky?
We’re after a Melecie, ya know?
It’d be too tiny to see.
No it wouldn’t!
Ta-daah!
I’m up on rooftops all the time,
keeping an eye out for all sortsa Pokémon!
You just wanna ride our ship, don’tcha?
Grrh!
Hey, you’ll let me, right, Roy?
Oh, I dunno...
Cap?
Please! Mr. Captain!
Your cooperation’s appreciated!
Guess we got no other choice!
Awright!
Let’s contact the Brave Asagi.
It’s proving tough to find...
The streets all look so similar,
I feel like I could get lost at this rate...
That’s precisely the kind of trouble that
detectives help people and Pokémon get out of...
Helping people and Pokémon...
That’s beautiful!
Melecie is a Pokémon that’s
born deep underground,
so perhaps it could’ve gone
somewhere like that.
Underground? A dark place, huh...?
I see, you have a point.
Then I know just the people to ask.
Wh-Whoa!
Amazing!
This is the Brave Asagi.
Excuse me!
Welcome.
A single loop over the city, was it?
Woo!
Amazing!
Nosepass, I’m counting on you.
A Nosepass?!
I’ve never seen one before!
Aaah!
Your nose is huge!
Eek!
Navi!
Y-Your nose!
Navi’s coffee milk...
Come on, you can’t
go scaring people, Metamon.
Your name’s Metamon?
Well sure, we know plenty about Miare,
above and below ground. Comes with the job.
Have you seen any Pokémon
wandering into any underground facilities?
A Melecie, huh...?
You know anything?
Now you mention it, just earlier...
I saw this huge dude carrying one
‘round the exit of the sewers.
Please, tell me everything you know!
It’s not anywhere...
We’re about to
complete the loop around the city.
Don’t lick that.
You like it?
You can have the rest of Navi’s.
Roy! Where are you right now?!
pOCket Monsters
Wonder Voyage
A big guy with blond hair,
wearing a martial arts uniform, huh...?
Apparently he’s near the sewers.
That’s him!
Where?! Gimme!
Ack! Hey!
It’s definitely him!
What do we do?
Let’s head down!
Look after the ship!
Navi, you wait here!
We’ll be right back!
Oho! Leave it to me!
Wait up! Wait up!
Whoa!
Wah! Sorry!
Countin’ on ya, Kairyu!
Let’s go, Taikaiden!
Wait up! Navi’s coming, too!
Hey! Kairyu?!
Thank you, Kairyu!
This’s the best!
Left down Automne Avenue!
Dot, you okay?
Go on... ahead...
Hey, look. The shape of the rock
on that Melecie’s chest...
It’s the old lady’s Melecie.
Let’s catch it quick!
Got it. We’ll head straight over there
as well, so wait up for us.
Don’t do anything risky, understood?
Hah!
I won’t let you get away.
Hmm?
I appear to be lost...
Now, where might I be...?
Ohh!
That’s some outrageous brute force...
Melecie looks scared...
Do we save it?
No, we have to wait for Ms. Matière.
But we can’t just sit here talkin’!
You’ve got a point.
Lucario!
Hurry!
Whoa!
Why are you here?
I am aware that you have been following me.
Navi, are you okay?
Yeah...
Same to you!
What’re you playin’ at?!
Strength is power!
Strength is justice!
“Justice”?
Indeed!
Ooh! What a surprise!
The Lucario accompanying you...
Is that not the Yellow Blast?!
Yes, but... how did you know that?
Ooh!
Miare City once knew a time...
when rumors spoke of its strength!
So what?
I have dreamt of battling it someday!
Allow me to ask...
What is your name?
Huh? It’s Roy...
As for myself, I am Shirou.
Mr. Roy!
Please, battle me!
Some lessons may only be gained
by vanquishing strong foes!
I want you to hand over
that little one.
Once our fair and just battle is through,
I would happily grant any wish you have!
Got it. Let’s do this, Lucario!
A 1v1 all-out battle! Got it?
I am counting on you, Tairetsu!
Tairetsu! Heighten your justice through
the strength of Mega Evolution, and claim victory!
Strength is power!
Strength is justice!
Mega Evolve!
The Tairetsu went and combined!
This is Mega Tairetsu.
We’ll do the same!
Gain true power
and surpass yourself!
Mega Evolve!
Mega Lucario Z!
Is this, then, the strength of
the Yellow Blast?
We shall demonstrate
what justice is!
Tairetsu! Brick Break!
Fend it off!
Metal Claw!
Tairetsu! Rock Slide!
Meet it with Infight!
Sense it with Guiding Waves!
Decide this with Iron Head!
Now! Luster Cannon!
The Yellow Blast...
Its dexterous movements live up to the rumors.
Yet, if it hopes to collapse
Tairetsu’s formation...
Its power is lacking!
Tairetsu! Last Stand!
Here it comes, Lucario!
And now you shall taste this!
Use Brick Break!
Lucario!
As expected of the Yellow Blast!
The Tairetsu’s formation is...!
Lucario!
It is time to claim victory.
Use another Brick Break, Tairetsu!
Lucario, use Turning Swallow Strike!
Aim for Tairetsu’s belly!
Bear it with your shield!
A clever stratagem,
yet lacking in power.
We’re not through yet! Lucario!
Now, topple them!
All right!
Not justice!
You did it, Roy!
Amazing!
Mr. Roy!
As expected of the Yellow Blast!
The battle went as the rumors suggested.
Power alone could not claim victory.
The strength to predict
the flow of battle is also...
...justice!
It was a good lesson.
You’re strong too, Mr. Shirou!
You were both amazing!
Now hand over Melecie, as promised.
Oh, of course.
Though I must tell you...
Melecie is not my partner. It is merely lost.
Huh? And you knew that?
Roy! Ult! Navi!
So, where did you find that Melecie?
My younger sister found it
wandering lost.
Hearing of its plight,
I myself began to seek its trainer.
Then ya coulda said so earlier!
We thought it’d been kidnapped...
We’re sorry for the misunderstanding.
As am I.
I forgot myself in the excitement
of suddenly meeting the Yellow Blast.
I will take responsibility for delivering
the lost Melecie to its trainer.
Thank you, detective.
Well then, everyone...
May we meet again!
Dear Melecie!
While it was lost,
someone very kind was looking after it.
Is that so?
There was someone like that?
My thanks to all of you, too. Merci!
I told Murdock
we’d all be staying here tonight.
It’s gone...
It’s gone! It’s gone!
What’s wrong?
I lost my Dream Ball!
Huh?
Which Pokémon was inside?
There wasn’t... one...
Huh?
I’d never used it...
What’s up with that...?
So you weren’t even a trainer yet?
So there wasn’t
a Pokémon inside it, then?
Well, that’s a relief!
No, it’s not!
Navi... There’s nothing we can do.
I’ll get you a different ball...
No! I’m gonna look for it!
It’s gotta be that Dream Ball...
It’s gotta be!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Friede here!
It’s time to Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie!
Today, it’s Tairetsu!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Tairetsu
Classification
Type
Height
Weight
Ability
Formation Pokémon
Fighting
Helmet Armor
It’s a Pokémon that always acts in a pack of six,
and is constantly changing something when in battle!
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
But do you know what that thing is?
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
See the answer after the commercials!
Oh! One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
Gonna give my motivation button a little tap!
The power of hard work is amazing!
(Ahem!)
But if I slack off I might end up devolving...
Well, that’s no good!
But now you mention it...
I know button mashing won’t help at all
So stop shaking this maiden’s heart already
(Stop it!)
Getting attached, but then they turn away
When things just don’t go the way that you want...
Isn’t it so fun? Doesn’t it make your heart race?
Doesn’t it make you all excited?
When I feel a spark...
I’ll catch it in a Cutesy Capsule
Face to face with the dream I’ve always imagined...
I’ve got electric jolts running through me!
I’m so lovey-dovey I can’t even move!
When I know change is still inside of me...
I’ll catch it in a Cutesy Capsule
then we can be together forever
We’ll conquer any obstacle!
I know our future will shine!
So let’s be friends!
Pick up you! I want you! Hit chu straight in the heart!
Pick up you! I want you! We’re right at the peak of our adven-chu!!
Oh! One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Time to announce
the correct answer!
The answer is...
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
Its weapon
Its formation
Its leader
B: Its formation!
Its formation
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
As it fights, it rearranges its formation
according to how the battle is going!
Okay, we’ll try it too!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
A new special attack!
Justice!
Next episode
Aww... Where could it’ve gotten to...?
It was empty inside anyway, yeah?
Just give up on it.
No! I’m never giving up!
Navi, let’s look for it together!
Next episode
With everyone looking,
I bet we’ll find it!
It’s gotta be somewhere in Miare City.
Guess there ain’t no choice...
I s’pose I’ll give it a shot!
Next episode
Everybody... thank you!
And so, to be continued
next time on Pocket Monsters!
A Dream Ball For You!
Huh? You’re...!